Are you going through a tough time right
now? Cuz I know I sure am. And whenever
I'm going through something tough, I
always come back to the Jesus house. Cuz
[music] this is a house of
transformation. When I bought it, it was
condemned by the city. Vegetation had
completely taken over the outside.
[music]
It was ready to be torn down. Now it's
got murals of Jesus cleansing the temple
and being tempted in the wilderness. The
owners [music] had completely given up
on this house. It was covered in vines,
and it was less than a month from being
torn down by the city. All it needed was
somebody to believe in it. And now when
you get here, you walk through the tree
of life door. And the first thing you
see [music] when you walk in is an empty
cage. Is the light coming on? The inside
was wrecked. Nobody had loved it in a
while, but somebody brought it back to
life with love and attention. [music]
The city had said this place was done,
about to be torn down, but I said, "Nah,
I ain't listening." The ceilings were
torn out of it. Nobody saw any value in
it, but I saw things [music]
differently. I saw a masterpiece in the
making. This house wasn't done. It still
had a few tricks up its [music] sleeve.
So with faith and determination, I
hand-crafted this thing with everything
out of wood. None of it was made in a
factory, and when it's done, it'll go
back to earth, [music] just like us.
When I ran into roadblocks, like the
city telling me I couldn't build a new
structure, even though there was an old
one back here, [music] I didn't give up.
Through ingenuity and creativity, I used
pallets and bamboo to build a tiki bar
in the back. And throughout the process,
I feel like I left a part of myself here
with this house. When I was building it,
people told me I was crazy. They said,
"You're never going to fix that turd
bucket." But look at it now. That's why
I'm back here now, while I'm going
through the hardest test of my life, to
remind myself that even when things look
toe up from the flow up, just like this
house, [music]
there's light at the end of the tunnel,
and it's not always a train. The Lord
does not test weak men, and the devil
does not attack people without value.
Keep pushing till you get to the top.
Eyes on the prize.